Inventory of the Overseas Weekly photographs
Hoover Institution Archives
- Contact Sheet 15538, 1969 July 28
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - patrols (Rocket Belt) - Lt. David Coates - Capt. Phil Gioia - Sp4 Wallace Horner - sheet A.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption sheets for rocket belt story - July 28, 69 - Sheet A: Frame 1: Grunts move through thick jungle. Frame 2: Machine-gunner wipes his sweaty face. 3-5: Alpha Co. grunts scan NVA tracks in muddy trail--some ought to print. Rest of roll shows troops going through their daily routine in the rocket belt. Guy pointing in frame 13 is Lt Coates, guy with sunglasses and towel wrapped around neck is Capt Gioia, Co. of Alpha Co. Guy wading across stream with rifle, bedroll and metal case is Sp4 Wallace Horner (frame 27, that is). Metal case contains mine detector.
- Contact Sheet 15539, 1969 September 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - patrols (Rocket Belt) - Sgt. Michael Gray - Sp4 Don Saucier - Pfc. Reginald Wyan - Capt. Phil Gioia - Sp4 Wallace Horner - Pfc. Leroy Morrrow - Pfc. Edward Atkinsons - Sp4 Joel Lewis.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet B: Frames 8-10: Resupply bird lifts off from open field near Alpha CP. 12: Guys wait to start patrol. 13: Capt Gioia goes over map while talking with one of his platoons. 14: Sp4 Wallace Horner checks suspected area with mine detector. 17-21: Pfc Leroy Morrow Jr. checks small pond with mine detector. 22-23: Morrow searches site of earlier NVA rocket launching for signs of more nasty surprises. 24-25: More shots of grunts. 26: Edward Atkinson tromps through bush. 27, 28: Sgt Mike Gray hosts a meal before going out on night ambush. 29: Sp4 Don Saucier humps machine gun. 30: Night ambush humps to their set-up point, guy with tense look is Pfc Edward Atkinson (frames 31, 32). 33, 34: Pfc Reginald Wyan (left) and Sp4 Joel Lewis (r) display a go-to-hell jacket.
- Contact Sheet 15540, 1969 September 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - patrols (Rocket Belt) - sheet C.
- Contact Sheet 15541, 1969 September 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - patrols (Rocket Belt) - sheet D.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet D: Frames 2-4: Medic cooks chow while guy with suspected Malaria lies on ground waiting for log bird to roar. 5-9: Cav troops demonstrate different ways to beat the rain. Some use clear plastic bags, other crawl under a forbidden poncho (see this week's hotline). 10-12: GI guides log bird into LZ.
- Contact Sheet 15542, 1969 September 6
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Col. Peter Wondolowski - Col. Rawls Frazier - Lt. Col. Kenneth Howard.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Cutlines for UCMJ Code Change Story - Two pix both contain same people: Left to right: Col Peter Wondolowski, Col Rawls Frazier and Lt Col Kenneth Howard seen discussing new courtroom procedures prior to being sworn as military judges.
- Contact Sheet 15543, 1969 September 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp4 Richard Johnson - theft - Lt. Col. James Miller (PM).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Captions for OW Pacifik stories - Marijuana story: Pictures are of Grey Haired provost Marshall. Lt Colonel James Miller. Pictures are of defendant, negro, Sp4 Richard Johnson, setting Navy to legal assistance office.
- Contact Sheet 15544, 1969 August 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - planes & helicopters - Pfc. William Crockett - Sp4 Jerry Zeranick - complaints.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for unsouped rool of tri-x continuing art for helicopter shoot up story - Aug. 8, 69 - Hirst - Three or four shots of a black GI pointing to the tail boom of a chopper. This is where the shrapnel hit and hopefully a patch or two night show up. I shot some shots of just the tail boom without anyone pointing. They were shot late at night. The black GI is Crockett and the white one is Zeranick, both quotes in story.
- Contact Sheet 15545, 1969 August 9
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Col. Peter Wondolowski - Maj. Dennis Hunt - Capt. John Naughton.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Art for judges story - Aug 9, 69 - Hirst - These are two contact sheets marked A and B that go with the three-story spread on the junior military judges. Both have group pictures of Col Wondolowski along with the subjects of the three stories: 1: Maj Dennis Hunt, balding with blond hair. 2: Capt. John Naughton, crew cut, blond hair. Please mark the pix that show each of these men apart -- mug shots -- there are several of Naughton and only one of Hunt. Also mark the best group show of Col Wondolowski and the other two, identifying as Col Peter Wondolowski, head military judge for Vietnam.
- Contact Sheet 15546, 1969 September 6
- Contact Sheet 15547, 1969 July 12
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Hospital - Dr. Ralph Young.
- Contact Sheet 15548, circa 1967-1971
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Sheet #15: Cavite City at night. Frame 2: Gate at Sangley Point. 3-6: Gobs and girls do folk dance in local bar. 7: Bargirl waits for business to pick up. 8, 9: Typical Cavite bar girls. 10, 11: Guys and girls inside another bar. 12, 13: Girls and gobs do the latest dance. 14: What the hell does this sign mean???? 15-17: More dancing at The Ugly American. 18, 19: Note sexy outfit Filipino chick has on (bare midriff and no bra!!). 20: Gob makes time with girl. Rest of roll: More dancing.
- Contact Sheet 15549, 1969 September 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Lt. Col. Harvey Latham.
- Contact Sheet 15552, 1969 September 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Entertainment - Bill Ellis.
- Contact Sheet 15553, 1969 July 25
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Over pacifik - July 25, 1969 - Boyle -- cutlines - A: Dead NVA soldier's hand sticks out from his grave. B: Tired recon patrol machine gunner takes a drag during a quick break. C: The recon patrol found this dead NVA "crispy critter" in a foxhole. D: A GI strains to hear the sounds of the enemy. E: The patrol checks out empty NVA spider holes. F: A GI hugs the ground after the demo man sets of a 500 lb. G: An M-79 man covers the platoon as it crosses a small river. H and I: A GI covers his buddy as the patrol moves down a path. J: Sometimes the going was rough. K: A radio man reads the inscription on a NVA's pith helmet. L: Lt. Alan Vitters, platoon leader checks out a disabled APC left during a recent battle.
- Contact Sheet 15554, 1969 September 6
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - patrols.
- Contact Sheet 15555, 1969 September 6
- Contact Sheet 15556, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - water.
- Contact Sheet 15557, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - American-Vietnamese relations - Montagnards.
- Contact Sheet 15558, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Ed Williams - Maj. Thomas C. Middleton - Capt. John Berry - Capt. Leland J. Brumley - Maj. David E. Crew - Capt. Robert F. Morasto - Capt. Tom Young - special forces.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet number one for Green Beret release story - Oct 3, 69 - Hirst - Frame 2: Jubilant defense attorney leaps in air at news. 5, 6: Maj Middleton talks to press. 7, 8: Capt. John Berry (left) and client Brumley all smiles. 9-11: Maj Crew fields questions from teevee people (expression in frame 10 is a beaut) 12-15: Berry, Brumley, Middleton, Morasco and defense lawyer Capt. Tom Young jubilant at news. Rest of roll berets and lawyers talk it over, Capt Young flashes peace symbol in frame 19.
- Contact Sheet 15559, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - crew - Marasco - Rheault - Boyle - Capt. Williams - Capt. Bill Hart.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Cutlines for Green Berets--sheet two - Oct 3, 69 - Frames 3-5: Newsmen wait to interview the berets, cameramen in 4, 5 has camera lens cap with peace symbol on it. 6-9: Marasco (shades & green beret match) is interviewed by press. 10: One more frames of press wating to get interviews. 11-16: Rheault being interviewed. 17, 18: WO Boyle being interviewed. 19: Three of the Green Berets walk toward cars (guy in middle with sunglasses is Marasco, guy on right is Capt. Williams, not sure who guy on left is, but I think it's Maj Crew.). 20: Marasco (left) climbs into auto. 20a, 21a: Maj Crew (head circled) talks to press. To the left is defense attorney Capt. Bill Hart.
- Contact Sheet 15560, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - Rheault - Brumley - Marasco - Tom Young - crew - Middleton - Berry - Helen Gibson (UPI).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Green Berets release cut lines--sheet three - Oct 3, 69 - Frames 7, 8: Reporter talks to Green Berets and a lawyer--from left to right those in front whose faces you can fully see are Rheault, Brumley, Marasco and defense lawyer Capt. Tom Young--building in background is where they stayed before release. 9: Basically the same as precedding flicks but faces from left to right this time are Rheault, Marasco, Crew and lawyer Young. 10: Same but faces this time left to right are Rheault, Brumley, Marasco, Crew, Middleton (partly obscured by lawyer Young's hat) and lawyer Young. 11-12: Same as above left-right Rheault, Brumley, Marasco, Crew, Middleton and lawyer Young. 13-16: Lawyer Young (left, background) and the client Marasco, the alleged triggerman (right, background, head circled in ink) talk to the press. 17: Marasco--head circled in ink--don’t know what the thing in the foreground is, could be somebodies microphone. 18-20: Defense lawyer Capt. John Berry (left) and the client Brumley (right wearing Green Beret natch.). Girl is Helen Gibson from UPI. Shot of Berry flashing peace sign might be good one. 21: Maj Middleton answers questions from press.
- Contact Sheet 15561, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - Rheault - Marasco - Maj. Marty Linsky - Edward B. Williams.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Green Berets release cutlines--sheet four - Oct 3, 69 - Frames 2-10: Green Berets and their lawyers are jubilant at news of their release. In frame 4, Col Rheault clowns for press (head circled in ink). Frame nine is best as they break into a flurry of thumbs up and peace signs. 11, 12: Faces of some weary newsmen, cameraman in frame 11 has lens cap with big peace symbol on it (circled in ink). 13-16: Marasco (cool looking stud in shades) talks to newsmen. Expressions in 13, 14 are great. 17-20: Rheault (right, head circled in ink) talks to his military lawyer Maj Marty Linsky. 20a: Civilian attorney Edward Bennett Williams shakes Marasco's hand. (Williams at right, head circled in ink).
- Contact Sheet 15562, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - Marasco - Tom Young - Brumley - Middleton.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Cut lines for Green beret release--sheet five - Oct 3, 69 - Frames 2-4: Marasco (left) and his military lawyer Capt. Tom Young (right) are all smiles after release. 5-7: Nox-nix pix of some of the berets outside their hotels. 8: Marasco (head circled) talks to newsmen. 9, 10: Happy Green Berets, Brumley (end) flashes peace sign as does Crew (center) while Middleton gives thumbs-up (right end). 11, same as 9, 10 except that Middleton grins and holds a small camera. Middleton on right end with head circled in ink. 12, 13: Mor Marasco. Rest of roll: Nox-nix shots of Green Beanies outside their hootch.
- Contact Sheet 15563, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - Marasco - Rheault.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - cutlines for Green Berets--sheet six - Frame 2: Marasco (center) and Williams walk toward Freedom Bird. Guy X'd is PIO for Bien Hoa Air Base. 3, 4: Rheault (center) head circled in ink and other Green Berets walk toward Freedom Bird. 5: Rheault (head circled) talks to press for last time before leaving 'Nam.
- Contact Sheet 15564, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - Rheault - Middleton - Tom Young.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Outlines for Green Beret release--sheet seven - Oct 3, 69 - Frames 2-7: Col. Rheault looking worn and haggard talks to first batch of newsmen to arrive at Long Binh after release announced. These flicks were among the first taken of Rheault after release. 8-12: Rheault (left, green beanie on head) talks to fellow-officer shortly after daybreak on the day they were release. 13, 14: Nox-nix pix of Berets outside hootch. 15, 16, 17: Maj Middleton (left) is congratulated by woman (right). Like I asked but broad wouldn't give me her name (or phone number). 18, 19: Defense lawyer Capt. Tom Young (at left) reads statement from his client Marasco to the press.
- Contact Sheet 15565, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - Williams - crew - Hart - Rheault - Capt. Jack Leonard - Capt. Steve Shaw - Berry - Brumley - Linsky.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Green Beret release cutlines--sheet eight - Frames 2, 3: Housemaid irons khakis for Green Berets (they wore fatigues home, natch). 4-6: Capt. Brumley processes out. Note poster on wall "Win a Medal." 7, 8: Capt. Williams carries suitcasee and souvenier VC rifle. 9, 10: Maj Crew strides out of his room. 11, 12: Crew (right) talks with defense lawyer Capt. Bill Hart. 13, 14: Col Rheault and bags. 15: Green Berets drink beer before leaving for airport (left-right Capt. Jack Leonard, UsarV PIO Capt. Williams, Defense Lawyer Capt. Steve Shaw, Defense Lawyer Capt. Bill Hart, Brumley, and at far right of frame profile Capt. John Berry, Brumley's lawyer. 16: Left-right Lawyer Hart, Brumley, Lawyer Berry drink beer. 17: Left-right Brumley guzzles beer, Lawyer Berry raps with others, officer (don't know where he came from, just joined the table), Maj Middleton and at far right reaching for something is defense lawyer Maj Marty Linsky. 18: Rheault (head circled) and another Green Beret (I think it's Crew) carry bags to cars that will take them to the airport. 19: Rheault (head circled) sticks bags in trunk while other Green Beanie hands them to him. 20: Rheault (head circled) chats with somebody then frame 20 sits in back right hand seat of car that will take them to airport (Rheault head circled).
- Contact Sheet 15566, 1969 October 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - special forces - Rheault - Williams - Brumley - Berry etc.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Outlines for Green Berets release - Sheet nine - Oct 3, 69 - Frame 4: Rheault talking to press--this probably the best shot of him. 5-8: Marasco shakes hands, flashes peace sign, talks into microphone. Guy with head circled in 6, 7 is Williams. 9: The hootch where the six berets sweated out their case. 10, 11: Brumley (left) shakes hands and chats with defense lawyer Capt. John Berry (right) frame 11 best of them. 12-15: Civilian attorney Edward Bennett Williams (head circled) talks to press. 16, 17: Left to right Capt. Bill Hart (defense lawyer), civilian lawyer Williams and defense lawyer Capt. John Berry.
- Contact Sheet 15567, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pfc. Curtis L. Jennings - theft - Narcotics.
- Contact Sheet 15568, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - 1st Lt. William T. (Tom) Coleman - black market.
- Contact Sheet 15569, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pvt. Yernon Cyrus - Disobedience and disrespect.
- Contact Sheet 15570, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Maj. Kenneth Roberts - air mission.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Caption sheet for: FAC story - Picture of pilot Maj Kenneth Roberts, marked with x on contact sheet.
- Contact Sheet 15571, 1969 October 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Pfc. Chuck Colgan - public information.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: OW pacifik - Cutline for PIO photographer story - Contact sheet No. 3: Subject is Pfc Chuck Colgan, pio photographer snapping pictures with M-16 ready for emergency.
- Contact Sheet 15572, 1969 September 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy officers - Cmdre. Albert S. McLemore - Capt. James E. Keys - Lt. James A Hopson.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for Evans trial--sheet one - Sept 25, 69 - Hirst - Frames 11-14: McLemore (head circled in black) walks toward courtroom. 15-18: Judge Keys sits in court prior to trial. 19-21: Hopson (head circled). At officer club trial break.
- Contact Sheet 15573, 1969 September 25
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Navy officers - Cmdre. Albert S. McLemore.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for Evans court--sheet two - Sept 25, 69 - Hirst - Frames 3-8: Ramsey. 9, 10: McLemore strides out of court after sentence. Frame 9: McLemore in front. 11-16: Reporters phone in stories. 17-19: The courtroom where for all intent and purpose McLemore's career ended.
- Contact Sheet 15574, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - planes US (sky raiders) - Air Force.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Cutlines for OW pictures - Contact sheet no. A: Vietnamese A-37 pilot taxis out of revetment (seen through his wing and bomb load). B: A-37 roars off runway laden with 500 pound bombs. C: A-1 Skyraider dives on enemy position, unloading bombs. D: Skyraider dives in for strafing run with 20mm cannon. E: A-1 Skyraider dives again, strafing.
- Contact Sheet 15575, 1969 October 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - planes US (sky raiders) - Air Force - Capt. Tran Van Nghia - 1st Lt. Tho.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: A-37 - in formation on route to target - pilot of A-37 - Jet Fighter Bomber - bombing sight - Lt Tho and Capt. Nghia - another flight - VNAF A-37 story.
- Contact Sheet 15576, 1969 September 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - planes - US (sky raiders) - Air Force.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Cutlines for OW pictures - Contact sheet no. 4 - A: A-1 skyraider coughs and belches smoke as pilot coaxes old but dependable engine. B: Pilot on unmarked pix is Harris, USA Capt.
- Contact Sheet 15577, 1969 October 11
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - planes (sky raiders) - Air Force.
- Contact Sheet 15800, 1969 December 27
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - MPs - airbases (Cam Ranh).
- Contact Sheet 15810, 1969 November 3
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - S. Sgt. Jim Fairfax - Art (soldier artists).
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Caption ID's with artist story - All paintings by Fairfax - 1: Huey Cobra gunships in action. 2: 175mm Howitzer firing (shell casings in foreground). 3: "If I'm Hit Take Me to NSA" (Naval Support Activity Hospital). 4: Surgery. Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for Marine Artist Story - Nov 3, 69 - All pix are of Fairfax, artist in procter's story with painting "CAP." All OW photos by Brent Procter. Don H.
- Contact Sheet 15813, 1969 October 27
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - religion - Rev. Richard Dickinson.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for story about secretary of chaplains visit - Oct 27, 69 - All shots on roll are of Rev. Dickinson. Don H.
- Contact Sheet 15814, 1969 November 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - traffic accidents (Long Binh) - Long Binh Highway - roll # 1.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for Long Binh highway story - Nov 7, 69 - Hirst - Sheet # one - Frames 2-5: Traffic flows around bike hit by car on Long Binh highway. 6-9: Bystanders talk to slightly injured Honda rider. 10-12: The injured Vietnamese GI is loaded rather urgently into ambulance. Rest of roll--mox-nix traffic shots.
- Contact Sheet 15815, 1969 November 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - traffic accident (Long Binh) - Long Binh Highway - roll #2.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption sheet for Long Binh highway story - 7 Nov 69 - Hirst - Sheet # two - General shots of the the most deadly road in the world as seen from MP Jeep. 17 and 18 are good ones for bad traffic.
- Contact Sheet 15816, 1969 November 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - traffic accident (Long Binh) - S. Sgt. Robert Littleton - Long Binh Highway #3.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption sheet for Long Binh highway story - Nov 7, 69 - Hirst - Sheet # three - Frame 4: Honan (right, wearing MP brassard) doing paperwork for routine fender bender. 5-10: Overturned truck in middle of Long Binh highway -- note how traffic drives right by it. 11-19: S. Sgt Littleton (head circled) and Honan (other guy wearing MP brassard) patch up skinned Vietnamese. Guy fell off his bike (in foreground). Series 15-17 is best bet. Frame 17 is ideal because you've got people riding by, looking, and guy grimmacing with pain as iodine is applied. 20: Routine shot of Long Binh Hwy.
- Contact Sheet 15817, 1969 November 7
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - traffic accident (Long Binh) - Sp4 Terry Honan.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Caption sheet for Long Binh Highway story - Nov 7, 69 - Hirst - Sheet # four - Honah (guy on right, soft cap, MP armband) fills out forms for routine fender bender--same one as frame 4, sheet 3. 8: Honan walks away from wrecked Lambretta. 9: Honan (center) eyes wreck as MP wipes head. 10: Angry passengers tell the MPs how the truck hit them. 11, 12: Honan (holding clipboard) examines the wrecked three-wheller, then talks to witnesses, 13-15, then diagrams it on clipboard with his foot on the fender of his jeep, 16-17, and then writes down the number of the truck that did the hit-and run. 18, 19, 20: Wrecked truck lies on highway.
- Contact Sheet 15829, 1969 December 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - L. Howard Bennett (Deputy Assistant Secretary of Defense) - segregation.
- Contact Sheet 15830, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Mil. Training - upgrade teams #2.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for upgrade teams--two - Nov 25 - Entire roll is of classes. From frame 2 to 13a is on claymores. Rest on ambush class.
- Contact Sheet 15831, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Mil. Training - upgrade #1.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for upgrade team #1 - Nov 25 - Frame #4: PF platoon members. #5 Sgt Lewis (1) and interpreter. Rest of roll is Ruff-Puffs watching class.
- Contact Sheet 15832, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Mil. Training - upgrade teams #3.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for upgrade teams--3 - Nov 25 - Frames 2-9: Claymore class. 10-12: Ambush class. Morning after in ambush position.
- Contact Sheet 15833, 1969 December 27
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - crimes - acquitial - Pvt Carl Mobley.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for Mobley murder trial - Oct. 24, '69 - Hirst - In frame 4a Mobley (head circled) is cuffed before he is acquitted of murder. 5a, 6a Mobley (head circled, left) and lawyer after he is acquited.
- Contact Sheet 15834, 1969 November 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - USO - fire - Barbecue USO.
- Contact Sheet 15835, 1969 November 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - USO - fire.
- Contact Sheet 15836, 1969 November 8
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Sp4 Scott Mcnutt - demonstrations.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - ID sheet for turkey fast story - Nov 8, 69 - Hirst - All shots are Sp4 Scott McNutt, guy who claimed he got shafted.
- Contact Sheet 15837, 1969 November 22
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - food (soul kitchen).
- Contact Sheet 15838, 1969 October 20
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Brig. Gen. H. S. Cunningham - Vietnamese bridge (reconstruction) - pacification.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Pacification--sheet one - Oct 20, 69 - Hirst - Frames 6a-8a: Moer shots of Cunningham, Cg 173d. 9a, 10: Some of the GIs involved in the pacification program atop the bridge they secure. 11a, 12a: Bridge demolished by VC (left) and new one constructed by 173d. 13a-15a: Gun truck that patrols the back roads (just in case).
- Contact Sheet 15840, 1969 November 29
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - EES - US civilians.
- Contact Sheet 15841, 1969 September 13
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Crimes - Maj. Roger E. Simmons.
- Contact Sheet 15842, 1969 October 24
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - Brig. Gen. H. S. Cunningham.
  NOTES ON CONTACT SHEET: Overseas pazifik - Contact sheet for story on Cg. 173d Abn Brig (sheet one) - Oct 24, 69 - Hirst - All shots of man with head circled on this roll are Cunningham.
- Contact Sheet 15843, circa 1967-1971
  ENVELOPE TEXT: Vietnam - VC [Viet Cong] defectors.